Stanford has just released their annual
report on AI. It's over 400 pages, but
there are two findings that I think are
worth noting. So, I'm going to mention
it here. The first is that basically all
of the large language models are
converging. Now, a couple years ago,
there's a big difference between the
best models versus the worst models.
Today, that difference is less than 5%.
So, basically, it doesn't matter if
you're using a paid model, free model,
or an open-source model. They are all
working pretty well at the moment. And
that that gap is only going to further
decrease and decrease and decrease. And
what this means is that basically, at
this point, artificial intelligence has
been commoditized. So, it doesn't really
matter which model you use anymore. And
the second key finding in this report is
that most businesses have not caught up
with the technology. The technology is
basically sprinting forward faster than
businesses can keep up. Most business
owners are still using AI like a
chatbot. So, you go on to ChatGPT or
Claude, you type in the prompt, you get
a response. But, however, AI can now act
as agents where they can start taking
actions. And that's exactly what I'm
going to show you how to get started in
this video. In fact, there are
pre-packaged agents that I will give to
you and show you how to find more on
your own as well. This will speed up
your learning curve and make it easier
for you to adopt agentic AI. Now, if
you're new to my channel, hi, my name is
Helena, and on this channel, I love to
talk about everything agentic AI,
automations, tech. So, if you want to be
in the know on the latest technology
advancements, please make sure you like
and subscribe, and this will help out
this channel so much as well. I've also
got a free course on agentic AI, and I
will show you in depth how you can start
building your first AI agent. So, make
sure you sign up for this free training
below as well. Now, let's get right into
it. A great hack is to find pre-built AI
agents for free on GitHub. So, there are
a lot of developers all around the world
who have spent hundreds of hours
building these AI agents and then they
just decided to open source it. There
are a couple of projects that are really
good and there are three in particular
that stood out to me and I'm going to
show you what these three projects are.
The first one is LOM console skill. So,
this is based on Karpathy's method. So,
Karpathy, he is one of the co-founders
of OpenAI and basically he invented this
method where there are different LOMs
that you can ask the same question to
like ChatGPT, Gemini, Claude, Perplexity
and they will debate each other in order
to come up with the best answers for
you. So, this skill and this set of
agents is a variation of that. Instead
of using multiple LOMs, it will all use
Claude though, but it still works quite
well. So, let me show you what's inside
of in this skill right here. There are
five advisors that will be computing
your answers in a parallel. You have a
contrarian, the first principles
thinker, the expansionist, the outsider
and finally the executor. Okay? So,
after you learned what this project is
about just by scrolling down on the
GitHub page. Now, another thing you want
to note is like how many stars and how
many forks it does in this particular
project have. When it has a lot of
stars, it's an indication that this
particular project is very popular.
That's another way to help you vet good
free projects versus the ones that are
just not worth your time. Now, the next
question becomes how do we load this
GitHub project into our own Claude
account so that we can start using these
AI agents, right? So, in order to do
that, you want to download Claude
co-work. So, in order to make any of
these skill sets that I'm about to share
with you work, you need to download the
desktop version of Claude. They will not
work on the web-based version, but it is
free to download this as well. Now, just
go to claude.com/download
and then choose your operating browser.
For me, is the Mac OS. Click here and
then log in to your Claude account once
you have this downloaded. This is what
it will look like once you have Claude
downloaded onto your desktop. You will
have three tabs here across the top and
you want to go over to the third one
that says code. Now, in order to get the
LM console GitHub project into our own
Claude, this is the line of code that we
want to put in. Basically, we're telling
Claude to clone the GitHub folder right
here and we want it to clone it into our
own Claude folders that is sitting in
our desktop, okay? And so, once we run
the skill successfully, this is what it
will look like. Now, we can actually get
our Claude account to debate each other.
We can ask it business questions like,
"Should I raise my prices? Should I
launch this product? Does it make sense
to do A or B?" I'll give you an example
of how I use this. So, I'm going to use
my fictional bakery company as an
example. So, you just type in something
like console this to activate the LM
console skill right here. So, I put in
console this, "Helena's bakery has a
monthly cupcake subscription.
Subscribers are loyal, but growth has
flattened. Should we focus more on
getting new subscribers or raising
prices and adding perks to the existing
ones? We also want to do this in the
next quarter. Should we either launch a
new referral program or should we open a
second location? Uh debate it." So, as
you can see, the LM console skill has
ran and we can see where the console
clashed and you can see all five of the
console members debating each other. We
can see the whole transcript here.
Here's what the contrarian thinks. Here
is what the first principle thinks about
the two questions. Here's what the
expansionist think. Here's what the
outsider think. Here's what the executor
thinks. And then, we can see how they
reviewed each other. And finally, here
is the verdict. They all agree that we
should monetize in the loyal base first,
not focus on acquisition. Here's the
blind spots caught by the console. And
finally, the recommendation. So, if
you're stuck with strategic business
questions in your business, you need to
install this skill set right now and
help you get unstuck. I use this almost
every single day. It's basically like
having your own team of board of
advisors for absolutely free. Now, for
the sake of time, I'm not going to read
you out the entire MD file, but I will
include it in the resource section below
if you do want to read this entire MD
file in more details. Okay, moving on to
the second set of skills that I want to
introduce it to. And this is called last
30 days. And as you can see here, it has
over 46,000
stars over on GitHub. So, of course, I
just see what the hype is all about. And
as I scroll down, you can see it's the
number one repository of the day on in
GitHub. And basically, what it does is
that it will scan through Reddit, X,
YouTube, TikTok, Instagram, Hacker News,
and all of these sites that you see here
for the latest sentiment about any
product, any service, any topic that
you're searching for. So, for example,
if I wanted to make a YouTube video on
the latest Claude IPO and its updates, I
can just now put  last 30 days
Claude IPO and it will go out and do the
research for me. Now, I'm getting ahead
of my of myself a little bit. Let's
first install this skill first. So, of
course, we're going to go up here and
click on new session. And this is the
bit of line that we want to put in. And
of course, you don't need to know how to
code. I will give you this line, and it
will be included in the installation
documents in the description below.
Okay, once I have this skill installed
into my GitHub account, I can see that I
get a confirmation here from Claude.
This means that this skill is now ready
to use. And so, now all I need to do is
type in the backslash line, and you can
see that this skill is now loaded into
my account. If you do do not see the
last 30-day skill when you type and this
turning blue, that means you have not
loaded the skill set properly. If it's
loaded properly, you will see this new
skill set in your Claude account now.
Now, I can ask it any question that I
want. For example, if I want to do some
research on Zapier, who is one of the
sponsors of this channel, I can say
something like this, "What are people
saying about Zapier in the last 30 days?
Give me the honest sentiment, the
biggest praises, the biggest complaints,
and whether you'd recommend it right
now." So, I can just type in this this
particular prompt, and then wait a
couple minutes, and this team of AI
agents will go out to X, YouTube,
Reddit, etc. to compile all of the
sentiment that users have been saying
about this brand right here. You can use
it for product research. If you're
thinking about starting a new business,
maybe you're using it to look at what
people are saying about the pain points
they have in the in the industry that
you're trying to work in. I mean,
there's so many use cases for this. It
is absolutely a game-changer for any
type of research that you want to do.
All right, so now this took about 5
minutes or so, and now you can see we
have a comprehensive report on what
people like, don't like about Zapier,
and where the point of improvements
could be. As you can see from the last
30-day skill, it is pulling the exact
URL where people are talking about your
industry, your product, or the pain
points that they have on the internet,
and it's giving the exact links to those
conversations,
and it's summarizing everything for you,
telling you exactly how you can
differentiate yourself from your
competitors or improve upon your own
products by seeing what the pain points
are and what people are complaining
about. So, I'm here um people are
looking for a human approval layer for
AI agents and it's Zapier workflows. All
right, score of 41. So, that is the
highest point of uh improvement for
Zapier here. Another And then the second
one is another cash grab from Zapier.
This is why I'm moving to make.com.
Okay, interesting. Third And then the
third one here is anyone generating PDFs
from Zapier without it being a
nightmare. This is another great idea
for a demo that Zapier can produce is
showing people how they can create PDFs
and invoices. And this is exactly what
people are asking for. I went ahead and
I ran the skill again by doing the
backslash last 30 days. So, this is what
Claude is on in this skill. And I put in
Claude IPO. Okay, and it went over and
it did all the research about
Anthropic's upcoming IPO for me, and it
summarized all of the user sentiments
here into this document. So, what people
are saying about it, what the
speculations are, what's happening in
the Polymarket, etc., right? So, it's
giving me all these URLs. So, if I
wanted to create an upcoming YouTube
video on the upcoming uh IPO of Claude,
like all the research is already
summarized here for me. And if I want
more details, I can click on all of
these links here. Now, just to show you
the difference between using last 30
days and using like Claude normally,
here is the result when I put in the
exact same prompt into Claude without
using the last 30 days skill. So, you
can see here is the Zappier sentiment,
okay? The overall vibe is still the
default, but the love is more
conditional than it used to be, and it
shows us some statistics here from G2
and Capterra, and it summarizes the
biggest uh praises here, and then it
summarizes and the biggest complaints
here, and then it gives us an overall
recommendation. So, you can see how this
result right here is very generic
compared to the last 30 days a document
that we see here with all the big exact
link and exactly what people are saying
with their exact wording. So, I did the
same for the Claude IPO, and you can see
when we're just using it without these
skill sets attached to it, the result is
very bland, very generic, and this is
how you can elevate your own AI and not
get it to sound like everyone else,
right? When we use these agents, when we
use in these skill sets, we get
ourselves to the top AI users instead of
getting the same responses as everyone
else, okay? All right. Now, I want to
move on to the third set of AI agents
that I want to give to you. And this is
actually created by Gary Tan, and he is
the CEO's of Y Combinator, which is
basically the world's biggest incubator
for startups in general, right? And he
released his entire team of AI agents
that you he uses to code and test
software. And this is really a
must-have. So, it has over 115,000
stars on GitHub. So, that means this is
super, super popular, okay?
And when we scroll down to the
descriptions, it tells us in the list of
AI agents that this entire project will
give you access to. So, it will give you
access to all of these AI agents here.
It gives you examples of how they work,
and you will get a CEO founder,
engineering manager, a senior designer,
design partner, staff engineer, tester,
design engineer, QA lead, etc. etc. So,
basically, when you download this set of
AI agents, you have an entire
development team that can do all of
these things for you for absolutely
free. Again, here is how we can now
download this entire team of AI agents
into our Claude co-work. Now, in order
to install Gary Tan's entire team of
development AI agents into your own
Claude account, just put in this piece
of code right here. And again, I will
give you this exact code in the
descriptions below so that you don't
have to figure out what to put into your
own Claude account here. And then, once
you copy and paste this, so press allow
once it ask you if it can install it
onto your local desktop. So, then you
just have to wait a few minutes for this
entire repository to be cloned into your
own Claude account. You may have to
click on allow a couple of times for
this entire process to finish. And once
the G stack skill finished loading, this
is the prompt that I put in it just to
test it out. So, basically, I told it to
build a landing page for fictional AI
startup called Nexus, which is an AI
agent platform that runs tasks for
businesses on autopilot. Then I gave it
some additional instructions here.
Another thing that you will see once you
have the skill properly loaded is when
you put the slash command, you will see
additional AI agents loaded into your
account. So, you can see I have the
diagram agent now, which matches. So,
another thing to note is that once you
have all of these skills successfully
loaded into your Claude account, when
you type in the slash command, you will
now see these slash commands here. So,
if I do office hour, you can see now I
have the office hour skill here, which
does in this right here, okay? So, I can
put in plan uh plan CEO review. You can
see now I have the skill, and I know it
does in this. It will rethink the
problem, find the 10-star product hiding
inside the request, and the four notes
expansion, selective expansion, hold
scope, and reduction, okay? So, I don't
have to reprompt everything here. I just
type in this skill right here after I
load it in that entire GitHub
repository, and now I can ask it any
product CEO-related questions. The same
thing goes for design review, for
development, for debugging, for testing,
etc. By using these three repositories,
you can see how now you can elevate
yourself from just using AI like a
chatbot to getting meaningful and more
detailed responses from AI that no one
else has. Okay, so it's been about 3 to
4 minutes, and our website here is done.
You can see it has a nice fancy 3D
graphic here on the on the back of the
website, and it moves as I'm moving my
mouse as well. I mean, this used to be
something that you pay a couple thousand
dollars for an UX designer to design out
for you, and another couple thousand
dollars that you pay a developer to
develop for you, and it probably take a
month or two to get something like this
up, but now it can be done within
minutes with one prompt.
Isn't that mind-blowing, guys? I mean,
my mind it was blown. Anyway. So, I hope
you can see now. This is how you can go
from just typing in a prompt into
ChatGPT and getting output to actually
getting much more meaningful results
from your AI and elevate yourself from a
basic AI user to the top 1%. Again, I
will include all of the instructions on
how to install all three of these
repositories in the descriptions below.
Thank you so much for joining me for
this tutorial and make sure that you
sign up for my free agentic AI
masterclass if you want to dive deeper
into how to build your own AI employees
that will work inside of your businesses
for your use cases. And if you got any
value out of this tutorial, I would
really appreciate it if you can like and
subscribe and I'll see you soon in my
next tutorial. Bye for now.